the following content is provided under a Creative Commons license
以下内容是根据Creative Commons授权提供
your support will help MIT OpenCourseWare continue to offer
您的支持将有助于麻省理工学院开放式课程继续报价
high-quality educational resources for free
免费优质教育资源
to make a donation or view additional materials from 100 to them IT courses
进行捐赠或查看其他材料从100到他们的IT课程
visit MIT OpenCourseWare at 0 CW
参观麻省理工学院开放式课程在0 CW
that MIT ided you
麻省理工学院被提供的你
home for
回家
the
该
in
the No
否
for last time
对于最后一次
we began to address the issue a building continuous-time signals out a linear
我们开始解决这一问题的建筑物连续时间信号输出的线性
combination of complex exponentials
复指数组合
and for the class a periodic signals
和该类的周期信号
specifically what this led to was the Fourier series representation
具体是什么，这导致了傅里叶级数表示
for periodic signals let me just summarize
对于周期信号让我总结
the result that we develop last time for
我们开发的最后一次结果
periodic signals we had the continuous-time for you
我们有连续时间为您周期信号
for a series where we built
对于一个系列赛里，我们建立
the periodic signal I dove a linear combination
周期信号我鸽子的线性组合
love harmonically related complex exponentials
爱谐波相关复指数
and what that led to was what we refer to as
什么导致了我们所说的
the synthesis equation and we
合成公式，我们
briefly address the issue love when this in fact bills
简单地处理这个问题时，爱情这其实票据
when this in fact is a complete representation at the periodic signal
这时候，其实是在周期信号的完整表示
and in essence what we presented was
而在本质上，我们提出了什么是
conditions either Forex city being square integrable
条件或者外汇的城市是平方可积
or X-eighty being absolutely inevitable
或X-80是绝对不可避免
then the other cited the for a series
然后将另一引为一系列
is what I refer to as the analysis equation
就是我称之为的分析方程
and the analysis equation was the equation the told us how
和分析方程是告诉我们怎样方程
we yet the forty a series coefficients
我们尚未四十一系列系数
from x50 and so this equation
从50倍，因此该方程
together with the synthesis equation represent
连同合成方程表示
the forty a series description for periodic signals
四十一系列描述周期信号
now we'd like to do is
现在我们想要做的是
extend this idea to provide a mechanism
扩展这一想法提供了一种机制
for building not periodic signals also I have a linear combination
为建设不是周期信号还我一个线性组合
complex exponentials and the
复指数和
basic idea behind doing this is very simple
这样做背后的基本想法很简单
and also very clever as i indicated last time essentially
也正如我最后一次基本上是很聪明
the thought is the following if we have a non periodic signal or a periodic
思想是下列如果我们有一个非周期信号或周期
signal
信号
we can think love constructing a periodic signal
我们可以认为爱情构建周期信号
by simply periodically replicating
通过简单的复制周期
that a periodic signal so
一个周期信号，以便
for example if I have in a periodic signal
举例来说，如果我有一个周期信号
as i've indicated here I can consider
因为我已经在这里表示我可以考虑
building a periodic signal where
构建一个周期信号，其中
I simply take this original signal
我只是借此原始信号
and repeated at multiples love some period t0
并重复倍数爱一段时间T0
now two things to recognize about this one
现在两件事情认识到这一个
is that the periodic signal
是周期信号
is equal to the a periodic signal
等于一个周期信号
over one period and the second is that as the period
在一个周期内，第二个是，随着时间
goes to infinity then in fact
趋于无穷那么实际上
the periodic signal goes to
周期信号变为
the a periodic signal so
的周期信号，以便
the basic idea then is
其基本思想是那么
to use the free a series to represent
使用游离的一系列代表
the periodic signal and then examine the 4e a serious expression
周期信号，然后检查4E严肃的表情
as we let the period go to infinity well
当我们让期间去无限好
let's quickly see how this develops
让我们赶紧看看这是如何发展
interns up the Associated equations here
实习生在这里的关联方程
again we have the periodic
再次，我们有定期
signal and what we want to inquire
信号和我们所希望来电咨询
into is what happens to the forty a serious expression for this
到是发生了40什么是严肃的表情对本
as we let the period go to infinity as that happens
当我们让期间去无穷大的情况发生
whatever for a series representation we end up with
任何一个系列的代表性，我们结束了
will correspond also to a representation for this a periodic signal
也将对于这一周期信号对应的表示
well let's see the forty a series
那么让我们来看看40系列
synthesis expressions for the periodic signal expresses
为周期信号表示的合成表达式
extol dirty the periodic signal as a linear combination
吹捧脏的周期信号为一个线性组合
of harmonically related complex exponentials
的谐波相关复指数
with the fundamental frequency Omega 0
与基本频率欧米茄0
equal to 25 divided by the period and
等于25的期间分割
the analysis equation tells us
分析方程告诉我们
what the relationship is for the coefficients
的关系是什么的系数
interns are the periodic signal now I indicated
实习生周期信号现在我表示
that the periodic signal and the a periodic signal
该周期信号和周期信号
are equal over one period we recognize
等于在我们认识一个周期
that this integration in fact only occurs over one period
这种融合实际上只发生在一个周期内
and so we can really express this interns
所以我们可以真正表达这个实习生
all our original a periodic signal so this tells us the for a series
我们所有的原始周期信号所以这告诉我们一个系列
coefficients
系数
interns affect safety
实习生影响安全
okay now
现在没事了
if in we look at this expression which is the expression for the 4e
如果我们看一下这个表达式是为4E的表达
coefficients the a periodic signal one other things to recognize
系数的周期信号一个其他的东西来识别
is dead in effect what
是死在什么效果
this represents are samples
这代表的样本
all an integral where
所有的组成，其中
we can think all the variable Omega
我们可以认为所有的变量欧米茄
taking on values better integer multiples
服用价值观更好的整数倍
Omega 0 said another way let's define a function as i've indicated here
欧米茄0表示另一种方式让我们定义一个函数，因为我已经在这里表示
which is this in a brawl where
这是本在争吵的地方
and we may think it will make a as being a continuous variable
我们可能会认为这将使作为一个连续变量
and then the forty a series coefficients correspond
然后在40的一系列系数对应
to substituting Omega
以取代欧米茄
is for Omega K
是欧米茄K表
Omega 0 now one reason for doing that as we'll see is that in fact
欧米茄0现在其中一个原因，这样做，因为我们将看到的是，其实
this will turn out to provide us with the mechanism
这将变成我们提供的机制
for forty-a representation affect safety
四十一表示影响安​​全
and this in fact and is an on below
这实际上，是一个在下面
all the four EA series coefficients
所有四个EA系列系数
in other words t0 the period times the coefficients
换句话说T0的周期乘以系数
is equal so this integral at integer multiples
等于使这个积分的整数倍
Omega 0
欧米茄0
okay so this effect tells us how to get the for a series coefficients the
好了，这个效应告诉我们如何获得的一系列系数
periodic signal
周期信号
interns love samples of an envelope and that will become a very important notion
实习生爱一个信封的样本，这将成为一个非常重要的概念
shortly and in
不久在
that in effect will correspond to an analysis equation
在效果将对应的分析方程
to represent the a periodic signal now let's look at the synthesis equation
现在来表示一个周期信号，让我们看看合成公式
group call that in the synthesis our strategy is
组呼，在合成我们的策略是
to build a periodic signal and let the period go to infinite
建立一个周期信号，让周期去无限
well here is the expression
那么这里是表达式
for the synthesis the periodic signal
用于合成的周期信号
now expressed interns
现在表达实习生
I'll samples of this envelope function
我将在包络函数的样本
and where I've simply use the fact that the substitution
而且在那里我已经简单地用事实替代
that t0 is to pile for Omega 0 and so I have an Omega 0 here
这t0为堆积的欧米茄0，所以我有一个欧米茄0这里
and a 1-over to pie and the reason for doing that
和一个1以上至馅饼和这样做的原因
as we'll see in a minute is that this then turns into an integral
我们将在一分钟内看到的是，这则变成一个整体
specifically then the synthesis equation
具体地说然后合成方程
that we have is
我们拥有的是
what i've indicated here we would now want to examine this
我在这里表示我们现在要研究这个
as the period goes to infinity which means that
作为周期为无穷大表示
Omega 0 becomes infinitesimally small
欧米茄0变为无穷小
and without dwelling on the details
并没有纠缠于细节
and with my suggesting that you give this a fair amount of reflection
和我建议你给这个反思相当数量的
in fact what happens as the period goes to infinity
实际上发生了什么的周期趋于无穷
is that this some Asian approach is an integral
是，这一些亚洲的做法是不可分割的
over Omega where Omega 0 becomes the differential
在欧米茄欧米茄的地方变成0差
and Omega and the periodic signal of course
和欧米茄，当然还有周期信号
approaches the a periodic sick so
接近周期性生病了，所以
the resulting equation that we get outta
由此产生的方程，我们得到失控
the original for a series synthesis equation
原为一系列合成公式
is the equation
是方程
that I indicate down here X if T
我指示下这里×如果T
synthesized interns all this
合成实习生这一切
integral which is what the forty a series approaches
积分是什么40了一系列的方法
as Omega 0 goes to zero and
欧米茄0变为零，
we had previously that XO maker
我们此前曾认为XO笔记本电脑制造商
was in fact an envelope function
实际上一个信封功能
and we have then the corresponding for EA transform analysis equation
对EA变换分析的公式，我们已经那么相应的
which tells us how we arrive at that envelope
它告诉我们如何在那个信封到达
interns love accept T okay so
实习生喜欢接受Ŧ这么好吗
we now have and analysis equation and
我们现在已经和分析方程和
synthesis equation which in effect expresses 4s
这实际上表达4S合成公式
how to build XFT interns or
如何建立XFT实习生或
if into tears and we finally space complex exponentials
如果哭了起来，我们终于空间复指数
the strategy to review it
战略进行检讨
and which I'd like to illustrate with
并且我想说明与
a succession of overlays was
覆盖继承了
to begin up
开始了
with are a periodic signal as
同是一个周期性的信号，作为
I indicate here
我在此说明
and then reconstructed from that a periodic signal
然后从该周期信号重构
and in this periodic signal has a forty a series
并且在这种周期性的信号具有40的一系列
and we express the for a series coefficients if this
我们表示为一系列系数，如果这
as samples all an envelope function
作为样本的所有包络函数
the envelope function is what I indicate on the curve below
包络函数是我在下面注明曲线上
so this is the envelope above the 40 a series coefficients
因此，这是上述的40一系列系数的包络
for example if the period t0
例如，如果在期间t0
was four times t1 in the 4a series coefficients
是四时间t1的4A系列系数
that we would end up with is this set
我们将结束与这一套
samples of the and below if
的及以下，如果样品
instead we double that period
相反，我们一倍期
then the Fourier series coefficients that we end up with
那么，我们最终用傅立叶级数的系数
are more finally space
更终于空间
and as t0
和T0
continues to increase we get more and more
不断提高我们得到越来越多的
finally space samples love this envelope function
最后空间的样本喜欢这个包络函数
and as t0 goes to infinity in fact what we get
和T0趋于无穷大，事实上我们得到了什么
is every single point on the envelope and that provides is
是信封上的每一个点，它提供的是
with the representation for
与表示方法
the a periodic sick let me just to
在一个周期生病让我来
really emphasize the point
真正强调的一点
show this example once again but now
再一次，但现在证明这个例子
let's look at it dynamically on the computer display
让我们来看看它动态地在计算机显示器上
so here we have the square wave in below it
所以在这里我们有方形波在其下方
the for a series coefficients we now want to look at the for a series
在为一系列系数，我们现在要看看了一系列
coefficients
系数
as the period at the square wave starts to increase
于方波的周期开始增加
and what we see is that these look
而我们看到的是，这些看起来
like samples love an envelope
像样品爱一个信封
and in fact the envelope for the Fourier series coefficients
而实际上在信封的傅里叶级数的系数
is shown in the bottom trace and emphasize in fact that it is the
显示在底部的痕迹，并强调事实上，它是
envelope
信封
let's superimpose it on top of the Fourier series coefficients that we've
让我们来塞给它，我们已经傅立叶级数系数​​的顶部
generated so far
到目前为止产生
okay now let's increase the period
好吧，现在让我们增加周期
even further and we'll see the for a series
再进一步，我们将看到一个系列
coefficients billion under that
系数十亿根据该
envelope function even more and in fact
包络函数甚至更多，实际上
as the period gets large enough what we
作为周期得到足够大的我们
begin to get a sense love is
开始得到一个感觉就是爱
that we're sampling more and more finally
我们正在取样越来越多的最终
this and below and in fact in the limit as the period goes off to infinity
这一点，下面，实际上在极限的时期熄灭到无限远
the samples basically will represent every
样品基本上将代表每
single point on the envelope well this is about as far as you want to go
信封上的单点嗯，这是你想要去的远
let's once again plot the envelope function
让我们再次绘制包络函数
and again to emphasize that we've generated samples a bad
并再次强调，我们已经生成的样本坏
let superimpose that on the forty a series coefficients
让叠加，关于40系列的系数
okay so what we have then is
好了，我们有什么，然后是
now are forty-a transform
现在四十变换
representation the continuous time Fourier transform
代表连续时间傅里叶变换
with the synthesis equation
与合成方程
expressed as an integral as they've indicated here
表示为一个整​​体，因为他们已经在这里表示
and this integral is what
而这个积分是什么
the four th series some went to
四TH系列有的去了
as we let the period go to infinity
当我们让期间去到无穷大
where the frequency go to zero the corresponding
其中频率变为零的相应
analysis equation which we have here the analysis equation
分析方程，我们这里的分析方程
being the expression for the on below
即用于下面的对表达
up to 40 a series coefficients for the periodically
多达40个的周期性一系列系数
replicated signal and in shorthand notation
复制信号和速记符号
we would think affects if T
我们认为影响如果T
and its Fourier transform as a pair
其傅立叶变换为一对
as i've indicated here and the Fourier transform
因为我已经在这里显示出来，而傅立叶变换
as will emphasize in several examples and certainly
如将着重于几个例子，当然
as is consistent with the forty a series is
为的是与40系列是一致的
a complex value function even when accepting israel's so would accept the
一个复杂的价值函数，即使接受以色列这样会接受
real
实
we end up with the 48 transform which is a complex function
我们最终的48转换这是一个复杂的函数
just as the for you series coefficients were complex
正如你级数的系数是复杂的
for real value time function
对于真正的价值时间函数
so we could alternatively as with the 4e a series
所以我们可以替换为与4E系列
express the Fourier transform it turns
表示傅里叶变换它变成
love its real part an imaginary part
喜欢它的实部虚部
or alternatively interns
或交替实习生
love its magnet to and its angle
喜欢它的磁铁和角度
all right now let's look at an example
好吧，现在让我们来看一个例子
love a time function and its Fourier transform
爱一个时间函数及其傅立叶变换
and so let's consider
所以让我们来考虑
an example which in fact is an example worked out in the tax that's
一个例子，它其实就是一个例子在税收这就是制定出
example 4.7 tax and missus are all familiar friend
例如4.7税务和太太都是熟悉的朋友
the exponential
指数
its Fourier transform is the integral from minus infinity plus infinity X
它的傅里叶变换是从负无穷正无穷X中的积分
thirty
三十
either the minus J Omega TDT and
无论是零下Ĵ欧米茄TDT和
so if we substitute in exit to the and
因此，如果我们退出在替换的和
combine these two exponentials together these two exponentials
结合这两个指数函数一起这两个指数函数
combined are he to the minus the
结合是他对减去
times a-plus jail mega and
次A-Plus和大型监狱
if we carry out the integration
如果我们进行了整合
love this we end up with the expression
喜欢这个，我们最终与表达
indicated here and provided
此处显示和提供
now in this is important provided
现在这是很重要的提供
that a is greater than 0
a是大于0的
and at the upper limit this exponential become 0
并且在上限这种指数变为0
at the lower limit of course it's one and so
在过程的下限是1，所以
what we have finally is the for the
我们所拥有的最后是对的
Fourier transform expression one over a plus
傅里叶变换表情一个比一个加号
jail make
监狱化妆
okay now this Fourier transform as i indicated
还好现在这个傅立叶变换正如我
is a complex valued function let's just
是一个复值函数让我们只
take a look at what it looks like graphically
来看看它是什么样子图形
we have
我们有
the expression the Fourier transform pair
表达式中的傅立叶变换对
either the minus eighty times a step and its forty-eight transformers one over
无论是零下80倍迈出的一步，其48变压器一结束
a place J Omega and I indicated
一个地点j欧米茄和我表示
dead that's true for a greater than 0
死了这是真的为大于0
now in the expression that we just worked out
现在，我们刚刚制定了表达
if a is less than 0 in fact the
如果a小于0实际上
the expression doesn't converge the
表达不收敛的
to the -84 a negative
到-84负
as he goes to infinity blows up
当他去到无穷远炸毁
and so in fact the 48 transform doesn't converge
所以实际上48变换不收敛
in the case except for the case were a is greater than 0
在除的情况下的情况下进行了一个大于0的
and in fact there's a more detailed discussion of convergence issues in the
而事实上有收敛问题的更详细的讨论
tax
税
the convergence issues are very much the same
收敛问题大同小异
the Fourier transform as they are for the four th series in fact that's not
傅里叶变换，因为它们是为4个系列实际上，这不是
surprising because
令人惊讶的，因为
we develop the Fourier transform out of consideration
我们开发的傅立叶变换出代价
for you series so the convergence conditions as you'll see as you refer a
你这么一系列的收敛条件，你会看到你引用一个
detailed
详细
tax relate to whether the time function is
税收涉及到时间的功能是否
absolutely integral under one set of conditions
在一组条件是绝对不可或缺的
and square integrable under another set of conditions
而根据另一组条件平方可积
okay now if we plot the Fourier transform
现在没事了，如果我们绘制傅里叶变换
let's first consider the shape at the time function
让我们首先考虑的形状在时间功能
and as i indicated way restricting the time function
正如我指出的方式限制时间功能
so that the exponential factor is positive in other words you the -80
从而使指数的因素是积极的，换句话说你的-80
detainees as he goes to infinity the magnitude
被拘留者，他去到无穷大的幅度
or the for EA transform
或者对EA变换
is as i indicate here and
是因为我在此说明，并
the phase below it and
它下面的相位和
think there are a number of things that we can see about
认为有一些事情，我们可以看到关于
the magnitude and phase
的幅度和相位
the 48 transform for this example which in fact we'll see
48变换为这个例子，其实我们会看到
in the next lecture are properties that apply more generally
在下一讲是应用更普遍特性
for example the fact that the 48 transform magnitude is an even function
例如一个事实，即48变换幅值是偶函数
frequency and the phase is an odd function of frequency
频率和相位是频率的奇函数
now let me also draw your attention
现在让我再请你注意
so the fact there'd on this curve we have
所以其实这条曲线上有倒是我们
both positive frequencies and negative frequencies
双方正频率和负频率
in other words in our expression for the 48 transform
在我们的表达式为48变换换句话说
we've it requires both or make a positive
我们它需要两个或作出积极的
and Omega negative this of course was exactly the same in the case
和欧米茄负，这当然是完全一样的情况下
the for a series and the reason you should
的一个系列，你应该的原因
recalling keep in mind is related to the fact that we're building our signals
回顾记住的是相关的事实，我们正在建设我们的信号
out of complex exponentials which require both
出复指数这既需要
positive values have Omega and negative values Omega alternatively if we chose
正值有欧米茄和负值欧米茄相反，如果我们选择了
another representation which turns and occasionally to be much more difficult
另一种表示果然偶尔要困难得多
namely sines and cosines that we would in fact
即正弦和余弦，我们会在事实上
only consider positive frequencies so it's important to keep in mind
只考虑正面的频率，所以要记住很重要
that in our case both with the for a series in the 48 transform
在我们的情况下都具有为一个系列中的48个变换
we deal and require both positive and negative frequencies
我们在处理和要求正，负频率
in order to build their signals
为了建立自己的信号
now in the graphical representation that I shown here
现在的图形表示，我这里显示
I've chosen a linear amplitude scale
我选择了一个线性幅度比例
and a linear frequency scale and thats one
和线性频率刻度和多数民众赞成1
graphical representation the Fourier transform
图形表示傅立叶变换
that will typically use is another one
将通常使用的是另一种
that very commonly arises and
这非常普遍，并出现
which all just briefly indicate for this example
这一切都只是简略说明这个例子
and that is was referred to
那就是被称为
as a boat imply in which the
作为船暗示在其中
magnet to is displayed on a large amplitude in like frequency scale
磁体被显示在一个大的振幅在像频率刻度来
in the phase is displayed on a lock frequency scale
在相位上显示一个锁定频率刻度
let me show you what I me here is
让我告诉你我我在这里是
the general expression for the boat reply body plot
的一般表达式作舟回复身体的情节
expresses 4s the amp with two interns
表达4S带有两个实习生放大器
the longer them to the base 10 the magnitude
较长它们在基座10的幅度
and it also expresses the angle in both cases
它也表达了角度在这两种情况下
express as as a function
表现为一个函数
love a logarithmic speak with yes so
爱一个对数说话是如此
here is the amplitude
这里是幅度
as i've displayed at and
因为我已经在显示和
this is a log magnitude scale a logarithmic
这是一个日志震级标度对数
frequency scale as indicated by the fact that as we move
由，在我们的事实所指示的频率刻度
include equal increments along this axis we change
包括沿着这条轴线，我们改变等额递增
frequency by a factor 10 and
频率由一个因子10和
similarly what we
同样我们
have is a display for the phase again
有一个显示器，用于相位再次
on a light frequency scale and I indicated
在光频标和I表示
dead there is a symmetry to the Fourier transform
死有一个对称的傅里叶变换
and so in fact we can infer from this particular picture
所以其实我们可以从这个特殊的图片推断
what it looks like to the negative frequencies as well as for the positive
它是什么样子的负频率，以及用于正
returns
回报
okay now
现在没事了
what we've
我们已经
done so far is to develop
迄今所做的是开发
the for EA transform on the basis
该对EA变换的基础上
the Fourier transform it a periodic signal on the basis
傅里叶变换它的周期信号的基础上
periodically repeating it and recognizing
周期性地重复它，并认识
that the for a series coefficients are samples of an envelope
该为一系列系数是一个信封的样品
on an envelope and that these become more finally space
在信封上，而这些越来越终于空间
as frequency increases and in fact
随着频率的增加而事实上
we can go back to are
我们可以回去的
original equation
原方程
in which we developed an envelope function
在此我们开发了一个包络函数
and what we had indicated
而我们曾指出
is dead the 4e a series
死了的4E系列
coefficients where samples of this envelope
系数在那里这个信封样品
we then
我们再
to find this envelope as
找到这个信封
the Fourier transform all this a periodic signal so
傅立叶变换这一切的周期性信号，
that provided us with the way and it was a mechanism
这为我们提供了方法，它是一种机制
for getting a representation for a periodic sick
获取一个表示为一个周期生病
now suppose that we have instead
现在假设我们有代替
a periodic signal are there in fact
一个周期信号的存在实际上
some statements that we can make about how the Fourier series coefficients
一些语句，我们可以就如何傅里叶级数的系数
that are related to the Fourier transform of something well
这是关系到傅里叶变换的好东西
in fact this statement tells us
其实这种说法告诉我们
exactly how to do that what this statement says
到底怎么做，今天本声明说，
is that in fact the forty a series coefficients
是，实际上在40一系列系数
our samples all the four EA transform
我们的样品全部四个EA变换
up one period so if
达一个周期，所以如果
we now consider
我们现在考虑
a periodic signal weekend in fact
实际上是一个周期性信号周末
get before a series coefficients that periodic signal
得到一系列系数之前的周期信号
by considering the Fourier transform
通过考虑傅立叶变换
above one period said another way the 4e a series coefficients
上面一个周期说，4E一系列系数的另一种方式
are proportional samples on the Fourier transform
是在傅立叶比例样本变换
one period so if we consider this
一个周期，所以如果我们认为这
a periodic signal computer its Fourier transform
周期信号的计算机及其傅立叶变换
and selected these
并选择了这些
samples that I indicate here
样，我在此说明
namely samples equally spaced in omega
即样本等距的omega
in by multiples are integer multiples
由倍数整数倍
love Omega 0 then in fact
爱欧米茄0，那么实际上
those would be the story a series coefficients
这些将是故事的一系列系数
so we can go back to
所以我们可以回去
are example previously
在以前的例子
with that involved the
用，所涉及的
square wave and now
方波和现在
in this case we could argue that if in fact
在这种情况下，我们可以认为，如果事实
it was the periodic signal that we started with
它是周期信号，我们开始与
we could get the 40 series coefficients
我们可以得到的40系列的系数
that by thinking about
通过思考
the four EA transform above one period
四EA变换上述一个周期
which I indicate here and then
我在此说明，然后
the 48 series coefficients other periodic signal
48级数系数等周期信号
in fact are the appropriate set
其实是一组合适的
samples of this envelope
这个信封的样本
alright now we have away
好吧，现在我们拥有了
love getting the for a series coefficients
爱得到了一系列的系数
from the Fourier transform one period we originally derived
从傅立叶变换，我们最初来源于一个周期
the Fourier transform one period from the 48 series
傅立叶变换一个周期从48系列
what would in fact be nice
什么会其实是很好
is if we could incorporate before a series
是，如果我们能系列结合前
in the Fourier transform within a common framework
在傅立叶一个共同的框架内变换
and in fact it turns out dead there
而事实上它原来死的有
is a very convenient way of doing that almost by definition
是这样做几乎被定义为一个非常方便的方式
essentially
本质上
if we consider what the equation
如果我们考虑一下方程
for the synthesis looks like in both cases we
用于合成看起来像在这两种情况下，我们
can in effect define of four EA transform
可实际上定义了四个EA变换
for the periodic signal which we know is represented by its for a series
为此我们知道是由它的一系列代表的周期信号
coefficients we can define
系数，我们可以定义
48 transform and the definition of the Fourier transform
48变换和傅立叶变换的定义
is as an impulse train where the coefficients in the impulse train
是作为一个脉冲串，其中在脉冲串的系数
are proportional with the proportionality factor
是成正比的比例系数
25 for more less a bookkeeping reason proportional to the forty a series
25多少簿记理由成正比的40系列
coefficients
系数
and the validity of this is
与此有效性是
more or less can be seen
或多或少可以看出
essentially by substitution specifically
基本上是由专门的替代
here is then the
这里是那么
synthesis equation for the four EA transform
为4 EA变换合成方程
if we substitute this definition for the four th chance for the periodic signal
如果我们替换了这个定义四个次机会的周期信号
into this expression then when we do the appropriate bookkeeping
这个表达式，那么，当我们做相应的簿记
and interchange the order some Asian and integration
和交换的顺序一些亚洲和整合
the in polls integrates out to
该民调集成到
the exponential factor that we want so
我们希望这样的指数因子
we have the exponential factor we have the for a series coefficients
我们有指数因子，我们有一个系列的系数
the two pies take care of each other and what we're left with
两个馅饼采取互相照顾，什么我们留下了
is the synthesis equation for
是用于合成式
a periodic signal in terms of the Fourier transform foreign it interns
一个周期信号的傅里叶变换的计算外来它实习生
love it's for a series coefficients right now
爱它是一个系列的系数，现在
we can just see this interns
我们只要看到这个实习生
love a simple example if we
爱一个简单的例子，如果我们
consider the example love a symmetric square wave
考虑例子爱一个对称的方波
then in effect what we're saying is that
那么实际上我们要说的是，
for this symmetric square wave this has
这种对称的方波这有
set up for a series coefficients which we work that previously
设置为我们工作的一系列系数以前
and which I indicate on this figure
和我上注明此图
with a bar graph and really all that were saying
用条形图和真的那么说了
is there whereas these free a series coefficients our index
在那里，而这些免费的一系列系数索引
on an integer variable K and their bars not impulses
上一个整型变量K和他们的酒吧不冲动
if we simply redefine or define
如果我们简单地重新定义或定义
the Fourier transform love the periodic signal
傅立叶变换爱情的周期信号
as an impulse train where the weights at the impulses
作为一个脉冲串，其中权重的冲动
are to Paul II times the
是保禄二世倍
correspondent for a series coefficients and
记者进行了一系列的系数和
this in fact is what we would use as the four EA
这其实是我们的四大EA​​用什么
transform love the periodic sick
变换爱情的周期性病
okay now we've kind of gone back and forth
现在没事了，我们已经走了样的来回
on and maybe even it might seem
上，甚至它似乎
likely going around in circles so let me just
可能兜兜转转，就让我把
try to summarize the various relationships
尝试总结的各种关系
and steps that we've gone through keeping in mind that
而我们通过牢记已经走的步骤，
one of our objectives was first to develop
我们的目标之一是首先开发
representation for a periodic signals and then attempt to
表示一个周期信号，然后尝试
incorporate within one framework both periodic
一个统一的框架两个周期内合并
in a periodic signals
在一个周期信号
we began with
我们开始与
and a periodic signal
和周期信号
and the strategy was to develop
而战略是发展
for your representation by constructing
通过构建你的代表
periodic signal for which that was one period
周期信号的，这是一个周期
in and then we let the period go to infinity as
在然后我们就让期间到无穷大
I indicate here so we have and a periodic signal
我在此说明，所以我们已经和一个周期信号
we construct a periodic signal
我们构造了一个周期信号
extol dirty for which one period
歌颂肮脏的哪一个时期
is the a periodic signal X still dirty the periodic signal has a forty a series
是一个周期性的信号X还是脏的周期信号具有40的一系列
and as its period increases
和作为其周期增加
that approaches the a periodic signal and
该方法的一个周期信号和
the forty a series of that approaches the 48 transform
在40的一系列接近48变换
all the original a periodic sick so
所有原始周期性生病了，所以
that was the first step that we took
这是我们迈出了第一步
now the second thing that we recognize is dead
现在我们认识到，第二件就是死
once we have the concept to the 48 transform
一旦我们有了这个概念到48变换
we can in fact relate the Fourier series coefficients
我们其实是可以与傅里叶级数的系数
to the 48 transform one period
到48变换一个周期
so the second statement that we made was dead
因此，我们提出第二个语句已经死了
if in fact we're trying to represent a periodic signal
如果事实上我们正在试图代表一个周期信号
we can get the 40 series coefficients have that
我们可以得到40个系列的系数有
by computing the for EA transform
通过计算对EA变换
one period and then
一个周期，然后
samples that for EA transform are
样，对于EA变换是
in fact the 4e series coefficients for the periodic sick
实际上，以便定期生病的4e的一系列系数
okay then the third step that we took was
好吧，那么，我们采取了第三步是
to inquire as to whether they're is a Fourier transform
询问他们是否是一个傅立叶变换
that can appropriately be defined for
即，可以适当地定义为
the periodic signal in the mechanism for doing that
的周期信号的机制，用于执行该
was to recognize that if we simply to find the Fourier transform
是要认识到，如果我们简单地找到傅立叶变换
the periodic signal as an impulse train where the in polls
周期信号作为脉冲串，其中在投票调查中
fights or areas for proportional to the for a series coefficients
打架或领域成正比的一系列系数
then in fact the Fourier transform
然后实际上傅立叶变换
synthesis equation reduced to
合成公式减少到
before you see recent this equation so the third step
之前看到最近这个方程，第三步
then was with a periodic signal
然后是一个周期信号
the 48 transform that periodic signal
48变换的周期信号
defined as an impulse train with the heights or areas the impulses are
定义为脉冲串的高度或地区的冲动
proportional to the forty a series coefficients
正比于40一系列系数
provides us with the mechanism for
为我们提供了机制
combining together the concepts war
结合起来的概念战
notation love before you a series and Fourier transform so
在你爱的符号系列和傅立叶变换，
if we just took I E very simple example
如果我们只是把I E很简单的例子
here is an example in which
这里是一个例子，其中
we have and a periodic signal
我们已经和一个周期信号
which is just an impulse and its
这只是一种冲动，其
for EA transform is just a constant
对EA变换仅仅是一个常数
we can think other periodic signal
我们可以想到其他的周期信号
associated with this which is this signal
这是该信号相关联的
periodically replicated in with the spacing t0
定期复制与间隔T0
the Fourier transform love this is a constant
傅立叶变换的爱，这是一个恒定的
and this of course has a forty a series representation
这当然有一个40一个级数表示
so the Fourier transform or
因此，傅立叶变换或
the original in polls is just a constant the Fourier transform
原来在民意调查只是一个恒定的傅立叶变换
love the periodic signal is
爱的周期信号是
an impulse train where the heights at the impulses
一个脉冲串，其中高度在冲动
are proportional to the forty a series coefficients
正比于40一系列系数
and of course we could previously have computed
当然，我们可以前面已经计算
the forty a series coefficients to that imposed strain
四十一系列系数所规定的应变
and those for a series coefficients are as I've shown here
和那些为一系列系数是因为我已经在这里显示
so on both these cases these in effect
这样就这两种情况下这些效应在
represent just a change in notation we're here we have a bar graph in here
代表符号只是改变我们在这里，我们有一个条形图在这里
we have been imposed strain
我们一直在施加应变
and both at the is simply represent
而无论是在简单地代表
samples of what we have above
我们有什么样以上
which is the for EA transform
这是对EA变换
love the original a periodic sick
爱情原来定期生病
okay now once again I suspect that kinda
还好现在我再次怀疑，还挺
moving back and forth and and trying to straighten out when we're talking about
来回移动，并与试图理顺，当我们在谈论
periodic in a periodic signals
周期性的周期信号
may require a little mental gymnastics initially
可能需要一点点的精神体操开始
basically what we try to do is
基本上我们尝试做的是什么
incorporate within one framework representation for both
在为一个统一的框架表示合并
a periodic and and periodic signals in the Fourier transform
在傅立叶周期性和与周期信号变换
provides us with a mechanism to do that
为我们提供了一种机制来做到这一点
in the next lecture I'll continue with the discussion
在接下来的演讲中，我将继续讨论
or the continuous-time for EA transform in particular focusing
或连续时间对EA变换特别侧重
on a number of its properties summer which we've already seen namely the
关于它的一些特性的夏天，我们已经看到即
symmetry properties
对称性质
we'll see lots of other properties that relate
我们会看到很多，涉及其他物业
of course both to the 48 transform and to the for users
当然同时向48转换和向用户
thank you
谢谢